pinoyjobless.com 2010-06-13

# Privacy Policy | Dine Laang!

## [Privacy Policy](http://pinoyjobless.com/about/ "Permanent Link to Privacy Policy")

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at my site http://www.pinoyjobless.com . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

E-mail Subscription  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Google and the DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to this site’s visitors based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Advertisers  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the ad companies: Google Adsense and Infolinks. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please contact me @ itot54joni@yahoo.com
